{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{2(2x + 1)} + 2}/{{1}/{2(x + 4)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(8x + 7)(x + 4)/(2x + 1)(2x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 7)}/{2(2x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 11)}/{6(x + 4)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 7)}/{2(2x + 1)} * {6(x + 4)}/{(2x + 11)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 4)} + {3}/{2}}/{{2}/{(3x + 10)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(3x + 16)(3x + 10)/4(x + 4)(3x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 16)}/{2(x + 4)}}/{{2(3x + 13)}/{3(3x + 10)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 16)}/{2(x + 4)} * {3(3x + 10)}/{2(3x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(2x + 9)} + {1}/{4}}/{{2}/{(3x + 11)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 25)(3x + 11)/6(2x + 9)(x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 25)}/{4(2x + 9)}}/{{3(x + 5)}/{2(3x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 25)}/{4(2x + 9)} * {2(3x + 11)}/{3(x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(4x + 3)} + 3}/{{2}/{(3x + 11)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "24(x + 1)(3x + 11)/(4x + 3)(9x + 37)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{12(x + 1)}/{(4x + 3)}}/{{(9x + 37)}/{2(3x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({12(x + 1)}/{(4x + 3)} * {2(3x + 11)}/{(9x + 37)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(4x + 1)} + {3}/{4}}/{{2}/{(x + 2)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "3(4x + 5)(x + 2)/4(4x + 1)(3x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(4x + 5)}/{4(4x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 8)}/{(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(4x + 5)}/{4(4x + 1)} * {(x + 2)}/{(3x + 8)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(x + 5)} + {3}/{2}}/{{2}/{3(x + 2)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "3(3x + 23)(x + 2)/(x + 5)(9x + 22)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 23)}/{2(x + 5)}}/{{(9x + 22)}/{6(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 23)}/{2(x + 5)} * {6(x + 2)}/{(9x + 22)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(4x + 11)} + {1}/{4}}/{{1}/{(4x + 9)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(4x + 23)(4x + 9)/4(4x + 11)(8x + 19)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 23)}/{4(4x + 11)}}/{{(8x + 19)}/{(4x + 9)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 23)}/{4(4x + 11)} * {(4x + 9)}/{(8x + 19)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(3x + 1)} + {1}/{2}}/{{3}/{(x + 7)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 7)(x + 7)/3(3x + 1)(x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 7)}/{2(3x + 1)}}/{{3(x + 9)}/{2(x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 7)}/{2(3x + 1)} * {2(x + 7)}/{3(x + 9)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(x + 7)} + 3}/{{1}/{(x + 8)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "12(x + 8)(x + 8)/(x + 7)(3x + 28)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(x + 8)}/{(x + 7)}}/{{(3x + 28)}/{4(x + 8)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(x + 8)}/{(x + 7)} * {4(x + 8)}/{(3x + 28)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(4x + 3)} + {4}/{3}}/{{3}/{2(x + 3)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(16x + 15)(x + 3)/9(4x + 3)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(16x + 15)}/{3(4x + 3)}}/{{3(x + 4)}/{2(x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(16x + 15)}/{3(4x + 3)} * {2(x + 3)}/{3(x + 4)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(3x + 4)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{(3x + 8)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(9x + 16)(3x + 8)/2(3x + 4)(9x + 26)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(9x + 16)}/{4(3x + 4)}}/{{(9x + 26)}/{2(3x + 8)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(9x + 16)}/{4(3x + 4)} * {2(3x + 8)}/{(9x + 26)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{2(2x + 3)} + {1}/{3}}/{{2}/{(x + 7)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(4x + 9)(x + 7)/2(2x + 3)(x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 9)}/{6(2x + 3)}}/{{(x + 13)}/{3(x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 9)}/{6(2x + 3)} * {3(x + 7)}/{(x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(4x + 9)} + {3}/{2}}/{{1}/{(x + 3)} + 4}\\)", "answer": "(12x + 35)(x + 3)/2(4x + 9)(4x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(12x + 35)}/{2(4x + 9)}}/{{(4x + 13)}/{(x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(12x + 35)}/{2(4x + 9)} * {(x + 3)}/{(4x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 3)} + 3}/{{2}/{(2x + 11)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(3x + 11)(2x + 11)/2(x + 3)(4x + 25)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 11)}/{(x + 3)}}/{{2(4x + 25)}/{3(2x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 11)}/{(x + 3)} * {3(2x + 11)}/{2(4x + 25)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 10)} + {3}/{2}}/{{2}/{(2x + 9)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(3x + 32)(2x + 9)/4(x + 10)(4x + 21)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 32)}/{2(x + 10)}}/{{2(4x + 21)}/{3(2x + 9)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 32)}/{2(x + 10)} * {3(2x + 9)}/{2(4x + 21)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(x + 9)} + {3}/{2}}/{{1}/{(3x + 5)} + 4}\\)", "answer": "(x + 11)(3x + 5)/2(x + 9)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(x + 11)}/{2(x + 9)}}/{{3(4x + 7)}/{(3x + 5)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(x + 11)}/{2(x + 9)} * {(3x + 5)}/{3(4x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 9)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{2(x + 3)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 35)(x + 3)/2(x + 9)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 35)}/{4(x + 9)}}/{{(x + 4)}/{2(x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 35)}/{4(x + 9)} * {2(x + 3)}/{(x + 4)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(x + 6)} + {1}/{3}}/{{4}/{(4x + 9)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(x + 18)(4x + 9)/3(x + 6)(4x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 18)}/{3(x + 6)}}/{{(4x + 17)}/{2(4x + 9)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 18)}/{3(x + 6)} * {2(4x + 9)}/{(4x + 17)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(3x + 4)} + {1}/{3}}/{{1}/{(3x + 1)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 13)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 13)}/{3(3x + 4)}}/{{(3x + 4)}/{3(3x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 13)}/{3(3x + 4)} * {3(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 4)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 2)} + 4}/{{3}/{(3x + 11)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(4x + 9)(3x + 11)/3(x + 2)(3x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 9)}/{(x + 2)}}/{{3(3x + 13)}/{2(3x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 9)}/{(x + 2)} * {2(3x + 11)}/{3(3x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{2(2x + 1)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{3(x + 3)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "9(2x + 3)(x + 3)/4(2x + 1)(9x + 28)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(2x + 3)}/{4(2x + 1)}}/{{(9x + 28)}/{3(x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(2x + 3)}/{4(2x + 1)} * {3(x + 3)}/{(9x + 28)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(4x + 7)} + {2}/{3}}/{{4}/{(x + 4)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(4x + 13)(x + 4)/2(4x + 7)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(4x + 13)}/{3(4x + 7)}}/{{4(x + 7)}/{3(x + 4)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(4x + 13)}/{3(4x + 7)} * {3(x + 4)}/{4(x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{3(x + 1)} + 4}/{{3}/{2(x + 5)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "4(6x + 7)(x + 5)/3(x + 1)(x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(6x + 7)}/{3(x + 1)}}/{{(x + 8)}/{2(x + 5)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(6x + 7)}/{3(x + 1)} * {2(x + 5)}/{(x + 8)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{2(x + 3)} + 4}/{{3}/{(x + 10)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(8x + 25)(x + 10)/2(x + 3)(x + 19)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 25)}/{2(x + 3)}}/{{(x + 19)}/{3(x + 10)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 25)}/{2(x + 3)} * {3(x + 10)}/{(x + 19)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{2(2x + 1)} + 2}/{{1}/{2(2x + 3)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(8x + 5)(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)(8x + 15)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 5)}/{2(2x + 1)}}/{{(8x + 15)}/{6(2x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 5)}/{2(2x + 1)} * {6(2x + 3)}/{(8x + 15)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(x + 10)} + {3}/{4}}/{{4}/{(2x + 1)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "3(x + 14)(2x + 1)/(x + 10)(6x + 19)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(x + 14)}/{4(x + 10)}}/{{(6x + 19)}/{4(2x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(x + 14)}/{4(x + 10)} * {4(2x + 1)}/{(6x + 19)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(4x + 5)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{(3x + 7)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "3(4x + 9)(3x + 7)/2(4x + 5)(9x + 23)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(4x + 9)}/{4(4x + 5)}}/{{(9x + 23)}/{2(3x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(4x + 9)}/{4(4x + 5)} * {2(3x + 7)}/{(9x + 23)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 9)} + {2}/{3}}/{{2}/{(4x + 7)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 21)(4x + 7)/4(x + 9)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 21)}/{3(x + 9)}}/{{4(2x + 5)}/{3(4x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 21)}/{3(x + 9)} * {3(4x + 7)}/{4(2x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(3x + 1)} + {1}/{2}}/{{2}/{(4x + 11)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 7)(4x + 11)/16(3x + 1)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 7)}/{2(3x + 1)}}/{{8(x + 3)}/{(4x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 7)}/{2(3x + 1)} * {(4x + 11)}/{8(x + 3)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(x + 5)} + {1}/{2}}/{{1}/{2(2x + 1)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(x + 11)(2x + 1)/(x + 5)(8x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 11)}/{2(x + 5)}}/{{(8x + 7)}/{6(2x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 11)}/{2(x + 5)} * {6(2x + 1)}/{(8x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{2(2x + 5)} + {1}/{2}}/{{3}/{(3x + 7)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(x + 4)(3x + 7)/(2x + 5)(6x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(6x + 17)}/{(3x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 4)}/{(2x + 5)} * {(3x + 7)}/{(6x + 17)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(3x + 4)} + {1}/{2}}/{{3}/{(2x + 3)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(3x + 10)(2x + 3)/2(3x + 4)(8x + 21)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 10)}/{2(3x + 4)}}/{{(8x + 21)}/{3(2x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 10)}/{2(3x + 4)} * {3(2x + 3)}/{(8x + 21)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 3)} + {1}/{4}}/{{1}/{(x + 2)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(x + 11)(x + 2)/2(x + 3)(x + 4)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 11)}/{4(x + 3)}}/{{(x + 4)}/{2(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 11)}/{4(x + 3)} * {2(x + 2)}/{(x + 4)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(x + 8)} + 2}/{{1}/{(3x + 7)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "6(x + 10)(3x + 7)/(x + 8)(6x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(x + 10)}/{(x + 8)}}/{{(6x + 17)}/{3(3x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(x + 10)}/{(x + 8)} * {3(3x + 7)}/{(6x + 17)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{4(x + 2)} + {3}/{2}}/{{1}/{(3x + 5)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "9(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/4(x + 2)(12x + 23)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(2x + 5)}/{4(x + 2)}}/{{(12x + 23)}/{3(3x + 5)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(2x + 5)}/{4(x + 2)} * {3(3x + 5)}/{(12x + 23)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 2)} + 3}/{{3}/{(2x + 5)} + 4}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 8)(2x + 5)/(x + 2)(8x + 23)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 8)}/{(x + 2)}}/{{(8x + 23)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 8)}/{(x + 2)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(8x + 23)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(4x + 1)} + 3}/{{1}/{(4x + 3)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(12x + 7)(4x + 3)/(4x + 1)(8x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(12x + 7)}/{(4x + 1)}}/{{(8x + 7)}/{(4x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(12x + 7)}/{(4x + 1)} * {(4x + 3)}/{(8x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(2x + 9)} + {2}/{3}}/{{2}/{(x + 2)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(4x + 27)(x + 2)/6(2x + 9)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 27)}/{3(2x + 9)}}/{{2(x + 3)}/{(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 27)}/{3(2x + 9)} * {(x + 2)}/{2(x + 3)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(4x + 11)} + {2}/{3}}/{{3}/{4(x + 1)} + 4}\\)", "answer": "4(8x + 25)(x + 1)/3(4x + 11)(16x + 19)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 25)}/{3(4x + 11)}}/{{(16x + 19)}/{4(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 25)}/{3(4x + 11)} * {4(x + 1)}/{(16x + 19)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{3(x + 1)} + 3}/{{2}/{(4x + 3)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(9x + 13)(4x + 3)/3(x + 1)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(9x + 13)}/{3(x + 1)}}/{{(4x + 7)}/{2(4x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(9x + 13)}/{3(x + 1)} * {2(4x + 3)}/{(4x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(2x + 9)} + {2}/{3}}/{{1}/{2(x + 1)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(4x + 21)(x + 1)/3(2x + 9)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 21)}/{3(2x + 9)}}/{{(x + 2)}/{2(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 21)}/{3(2x + 9)} * {2(x + 1)}/{(x + 2)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(3x + 10)} + {1}/{3}}/{{2}/{(3x + 4)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 16)(3x + 4)/(3x + 10)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 16)}/{3(3x + 10)}}/{{(3x + 10)}/{3(3x + 4)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 16)}/{3(3x + 10)} * {3(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 10)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(3x + 8)} + {1}/{3}}/{{3}/{(4x + 11)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 17)(4x + 11)/36(3x + 8)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 17)}/{3(3x + 8)}}/{{12(x + 3)}/{(4x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 17)}/{3(3x + 8)} * {(4x + 11)}/{12(x + 3)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(4x + 1)} + {3}/{2}}/{{3}/{(4x + 3)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "9(4x + 3)(4x + 3)/2(4x + 1)(16x + 21)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(4x + 3)}/{2(4x + 1)}}/{{(16x + 21)}/{3(4x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(4x + 3)}/{2(4x + 1)} * {3(4x + 3)}/{(16x + 21)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(3x + 8)} + {1}/{3}}/{{1}/{2(2x + 5)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 17)(2x + 5)/3(3x + 8)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 17)}/{3(3x + 8)}}/{{(x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 17)}/{3(3x + 8)} * {(2x + 5)}/{(x + 3)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(2x + 3)} + 4}/{{1}/{4(x + 2)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "32(x + 2)(x + 2)/(2x + 3)(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{8(x + 2)}/{(2x + 3)}}/{{(2x + 5)}/{4(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({8(x + 2)}/{(2x + 3)} * {4(x + 2)}/{(2x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(2x + 3)} + {1}/{2}}/{{2}/{(3x + 8)} + 4}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)(3x + 8)/4(2x + 3)(6x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{2(2x + 3)}}/{{2(6x + 17)}/{(3x + 8)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{2(2x + 3)} * {(3x + 8)}/{2(6x + 17)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 5)} + {3}/{4}}/{{3}/{(2x + 3)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 23)(2x + 3)/2(x + 5)(2x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 23)}/{4(x + 5)}}/{{(2x + 9)}/{2(2x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 23)}/{4(x + 5)} * {2(2x + 3)}/{(2x + 9)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 2)} + {1}/{3}}/{{1}/{(3x + 8)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(x + 8)(3x + 8)/(x + 2)(12x + 35)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 8)}/{3(x + 2)}}/{{(12x + 35)}/{3(3x + 8)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 8)}/{3(x + 2)} * {3(3x + 8)}/{(12x + 35)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{2(x + 3)} + {2}/{3}}/{{1}/{(3x + 1)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(4x + 21)(3x + 1)/2(x + 3)(12x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 21)}/{6(x + 3)}}/{{(12x + 7)}/{3(3x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 21)}/{6(x + 3)} * {3(3x + 1)}/{(12x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(2x + 1)} + {3}/{4}}/{{2}/{(3x + 2)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "(6x + 11)(3x + 2)/4(2x + 1)(9x + 8)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(6x + 11)}/{4(2x + 1)}}/{{(9x + 8)}/{(3x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(6x + 11)}/{4(2x + 1)} * {(3x + 2)}/{(9x + 8)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(2x + 9)} + {1}/{2}}/{{1}/{4(x + 1)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "6(2x + 13)(x + 1)/(2x + 9)(4x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 13)}/{2(2x + 9)}}/{{(4x + 7)}/{12(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 13)}/{2(2x + 9)} * {12(x + 1)}/{(4x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(4x + 3)} + 2}/{{1}/{2(x + 2)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(8x + 9)(x + 2)/(4x + 3)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 9)}/{(4x + 3)}}/{{(x + 3)}/{2(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 9)}/{(4x + 3)} * {2(x + 2)}/{(x + 3)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(2x + 5)} + {1}/{4}}/{{1}/{(4x + 1)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 9)(4x + 1)/(2x + 5)(12x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 9)}/{4(2x + 5)}}/{{(12x + 7)}/{4(4x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 9)}/{4(2x + 5)} * {4(4x + 1)}/{(12x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(x + 11)} + {1}/{2}}/{{4}/{(x + 11)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(x + 19)/8(x + 14)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 19)}/{2(x + 11)}}/{{4(x + 14)}/{3(x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 19)}/{2(x + 11)} * {3(x + 11)}/{4(x + 14)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(3x + 4)} + {3}/{4}}/{{4}/{(2x + 7)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(9x + 28)(2x + 7)/2(3x + 4)(2x + 15)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(9x + 28)}/{4(3x + 4)}}/{{(2x + 15)}/{2(2x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(9x + 28)}/{4(3x + 4)} * {2(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 15)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 5)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{(x + 3)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 23)(x + 3)/4(x + 5)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 23)}/{4(x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 10)}/{(x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 23)}/{4(x + 5)} * {(x + 3)}/{(3x + 10)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(4x + 1)} + {2}/{3}}/{{3}/{(2x + 7)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(8x + 11)(2x + 7)/3(4x + 1)(2x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 11)}/{3(4x + 1)}}/{{(2x + 13)}/{2(2x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 11)}/{3(4x + 1)} * {2(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(3x + 10)} + {2}/{3}}/{{2}/{(2x + 7)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(6x + 29)(2x + 7)/2(3x + 10)(4x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(6x + 29)}/{3(3x + 10)}}/{{2(4x + 17)}/{3(2x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(6x + 29)}/{3(3x + 10)} * {3(2x + 7)}/{2(4x + 17)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 3)} + 2}/{{2}/{(4x + 5)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 7)(4x + 5)/4(x + 3)(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 7)}/{(x + 3)}}/{{4(2x + 3)}/{(4x + 5)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 7)}/{(x + 3)} * {(4x + 5)}/{4(2x + 3)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 6)} + 4}/{{2}/{(3x + 7)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "4(4x + 25)(3x + 7)/(x + 6)(9x + 29)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 25)}/{(x + 6)}}/{{(9x + 29)}/{4(3x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 25)}/{(x + 6)} * {4(3x + 7)}/{(9x + 29)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 2)} + {1}/{4}}/{{1}/{(2x + 11)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "(x + 6)(2x + 11)/(x + 2)(6x + 37)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 6)}/{4(x + 2)}}/{{(6x + 37)}/{4(2x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 6)}/{4(x + 2)} * {4(2x + 11)}/{(6x + 37)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{3(x + 3)} + {1}/{2}}/{{1}/{4(x + 1)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "2(3x + 17)(x + 1)/3(x + 3)(12x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 17)}/{6(x + 3)}}/{{(12x + 13)}/{4(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 17)}/{6(x + 3)} * {4(x + 1)}/{(12x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(4x + 7)} + {1}/{2}}/{{3}/{(3x + 10)} + {1}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "2(4x + 15)(3x + 10)/(4x + 7)(3x + 22)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 15)}/{2(4x + 7)}}/{{(3x + 22)}/{4(3x + 10)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 15)}/{2(4x + 7)} * {4(3x + 10)}/{(3x + 22)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(3x + 1)} + {1}/{2}}/{{4}/{(2x + 1)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(3x + 5)(2x + 1)/4(3x + 1)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{2(3x + 1)}}/{{2(2x + 7)}/{3(2x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{2(3x + 1)} * {3(2x + 1)}/{2(2x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 3)} + {1}/{4}}/{{2}/{(3x + 2)} + {1}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "(x + 11)(3x + 2)/(x + 3)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 11)}/{4(x + 3)}}/{{(3x + 10)}/{4(3x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 11)}/{4(x + 3)} * {4(3x + 2)}/{(3x + 10)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 5)} + 4}/{{3}/{4(x + 1)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "4(4x + 21)(x + 1)/3(x + 5)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 21)}/{(x + 5)}}/{{3(4x + 5)}/{4(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 21)}/{(x + 5)} * {4(x + 1)}/{3(4x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(2x + 1)} + {1}/{3}}/{{2}/{(2x + 1)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "1/2", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(x + 2)}/{3(2x + 1)}}/{{4(x + 2)}/{3(2x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(x + 2)}/{3(2x + 1)} * {3(2x + 1)}/{4(x + 2)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 1)} + 3}/{{3}/{(3x + 8)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(3x + 4)(3x + 8)/(x + 1)(3x + 14)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 4)}/{(x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 14)}/{2(3x + 8)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 4)}/{(x + 1)} * {2(3x + 8)}/{(3x + 14)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{2(x + 2)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{(4x + 11)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "9(x + 4)(4x + 11)/4(x + 2)(8x + 25)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(x + 4)}/{4(x + 2)}}/{{(8x + 25)}/{3(4x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(x + 4)}/{4(x + 2)} * {3(4x + 11)}/{(8x + 25)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{3(x + 1)} + {4}/{3}}/{{4}/{(4x + 3)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(4x + 3)/6(x + 1)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 5)}/{3(x + 1)}}/{{2(4x + 5)}/{(4x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 5)}/{3(x + 1)} * {(4x + 3)}/{2(4x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{3(x + 3)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{(x + 1)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(9x + 43)(x + 1)/6(x + 3)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(9x + 43)}/{12(x + 3)}}/{{(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(9x + 43)}/{12(x + 3)} * {2(x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(2x + 5)} + 2}/{{3}/{(3x + 4)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "6(2x + 7)(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)(3x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 13)}/{3(3x + 4)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 5)} * {3(3x + 4)}/{(3x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(4x + 11)} + {3}/{2}}/{{2}/{(2x + 9)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "(12x + 41)(2x + 9)/2(4x + 11)(6x + 29)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(12x + 41)}/{2(4x + 11)}}/{{(6x + 29)}/{(2x + 9)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(12x + 41)}/{2(4x + 11)} * {(2x + 9)}/{(6x + 29)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{2(2x + 5)} + {2}/{3}}/{{4}/{(3x + 8)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(8x + 23)(3x + 8)/4(2x + 5)(3x + 14)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 23)}/{6(2x + 5)}}/{{2(3x + 14)}/{3(3x + 8)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 23)}/{6(2x + 5)} * {3(3x + 8)}/{2(3x + 14)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{4(x + 2)} + 2}/{{2}/{(2x + 1)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(8x + 19)(2x + 1)/8(x + 2)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 19)}/{4(x + 2)}}/{{2(4x + 5)}/{3(2x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 19)}/{4(x + 2)} * {3(2x + 1)}/{2(4x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(2x + 5)} + {1}/{2}}/{{1}/{(2x + 11)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "2(2x + 7)(2x + 11)/(2x + 5)(6x + 37)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 7)}/{2(2x + 5)}}/{{(6x + 37)}/{4(2x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 7)}/{2(2x + 5)} * {4(2x + 11)}/{(6x + 37)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(x + 8)} + {4}/{3}}/{{2}/{(x + 11)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "8(x + 11)(x + 11)/3(x + 8)(x + 15)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{4(x + 11)}/{3(x + 8)}}/{{(x + 15)}/{2(x + 11)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({4(x + 11)}/{3(x + 8)} * {2(x + 11)}/{(x + 15)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 1)} + {2}/{3}}/{{3}/{(x + 6)} + {1}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 5)(x + 6)/(x + 1)(x + 15)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 5)}/{3(x + 1)}}/{{(x + 15)}/{3(x + 6)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 5)}/{3(x + 1)} * {3(x + 6)}/{(x + 15)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{4(x + 2)} + 2}/{{2}/{(2x + 7)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "(8x + 19)(2x + 7)/(x + 2)(6x + 29)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 19)}/{4(x + 2)}}/{{(6x + 29)}/{4(2x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 19)}/{4(x + 2)} * {4(2x + 7)}/{(6x + 29)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 1)} + {3}/{2}}/{{1}/{(x + 3)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)(x + 3)/(x + 1)(3x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 1)}}/{{(3x + 11)}/{2(x + 3)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 5)}/{2(x + 1)} * {2(x + 3)}/{(3x + 11)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(2x + 5)} + {2}/{3}}/{{4}/{(3x + 4)} + {3}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "8(x + 4)(3x + 4)/3(2x + 5)(9x + 20)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{4(x + 4)}/{3(2x + 5)}}/{{(9x + 20)}/{2(3x + 4)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({4(x + 4)}/{3(2x + 5)} * {2(3x + 4)}/{(9x + 20)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{3(x + 3)} + 4}/{{4}/{(4x + 9)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "4(12x + 37)(4x + 9)/3(x + 3)(12x + 43)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(12x + 37)}/{3(x + 3)}}/{{(12x + 43)}/{4(4x + 9)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(12x + 37)}/{3(x + 3)} * {4(4x + 9)}/{(12x + 43)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 1)} + {1}/{3}}/{{2}/{(x + 2)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(x + 4)(x + 2)/6(x + 1)(x + 3)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 4)}/{3(x + 1)}}/{{2(x + 3)}/{(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 4)}/{3(x + 1)} * {(x + 2)}/{2(x + 3)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 4)} + {1}/{2}}/{{1}/{3(x + 1)} + {1}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "6(x + 6)(x + 1)/(x + 4)(3x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 6)}/{2(x + 4)}}/{{(3x + 7)}/{12(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 6)}/{2(x + 4)} * {12(x + 1)}/{(3x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{3(x + 3)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{3(x + 2)} + 3}\\)", "answer": "(9x + 35)(x + 2)/4(x + 3)(9x + 19)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(9x + 35)}/{12(x + 3)}}/{{(9x + 19)}/{3(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(9x + 35)}/{12(x + 3)} * {3(x + 2)}/{(9x + 19)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 2)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{2(x + 1)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(3x + 10)(x + 1)/2(x + 2)(8x + 11)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 10)}/{4(x + 2)}}/{{(8x + 11)}/{6(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 10)}/{4(x + 2)} * {6(x + 1)}/{(8x + 11)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(3x + 5)} + {1}/{2}}/{{3}/{(3x + 2)} + {3}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "2(x + 3)(3x + 2)/3(3x + 5)(x + 2)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{3(x + 3)}/{2(3x + 5)}}/{{9(x + 2)}/{4(3x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({3(x + 3)}/{2(3x + 5)} * {4(3x + 2)}/{9(x + 2)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(4x + 11)} + 2}/{{4}/{(4x + 1)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "2(8x + 23)(4x + 1)/(4x + 11)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(8x + 23)}/{(4x + 11)}}/{{(4x + 9)}/{2(4x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(8x + 23)}/{(4x + 11)} * {2(4x + 1)}/{(4x + 9)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{(x + 6)} + {1}/{2}}/{{1}/{(3x + 10)} + 2}\\)", "answer": "(x + 8)(3x + 10)/6(x + 6)(2x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 8)}/{2(x + 6)}}/{{3(2x + 7)}/{(3x + 10)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 8)}/{2(x + 6)} * {(3x + 10)}/{3(2x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(2x + 5)} + {1}/{4}}/{{3}/{(3x + 1)} + {4}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(2x + 13)(3x + 1)/4(2x + 5)(12x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(2x + 13)}/{4(2x + 5)}}/{{(12x + 13)}/{3(3x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(2x + 13)}/{4(2x + 5)} * {3(3x + 1)}/{(12x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(2x + 5)} + 3}/{{2}/{(3x + 1)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "12(x + 3)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{6(x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(3x + 5)}/{2(3x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({6(x + 3)}/{(2x + 5)} * {2(3x + 1)}/{(3x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(x + 11)} + {2}/{3}}/{{3}/{2(2x + 1)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "4(x + 17)(2x + 1)/(x + 11)(8x + 13)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(x + 17)}/{3(x + 11)}}/{{(8x + 13)}/{6(2x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(x + 17)}/{3(x + 11)} * {6(2x + 1)}/{(8x + 13)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(2x + 5)} + 2}/{{3}/{2(x + 1)} + {1}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "8(2x + 7)(x + 1)/(2x + 5)(x + 7)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 5)}}/{{(x + 7)}/{4(x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(2x + 7)}/{(2x + 5)} * {4(x + 1)}/{(x + 7)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{1}/{2(x + 4)} + {1}/{2}}/{{1}/{(4x + 7)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "(x + 5)(4x + 7)/(x + 4)(4x + 9)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(x + 5)}/{2(x + 4)}}/{{(4x + 9)}/{2(4x + 7)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(x + 5)}/{2(x + 4)} * {2(4x + 7)}/{(4x + 9)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{4}/{(3x + 8)} + {3}/{4}}/{{1}/{3(x + 2)} + {1}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "3(9x + 40)(x + 2)/(3x + 8)(3x + 10)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(9x + 40)}/{4(3x + 8)}}/{{(3x + 10)}/{12(x + 2)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(9x + 40)}/{4(3x + 8)} * {12(x + 2)}/{(3x + 10)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 3)} + {2}/{3}}/{{4}/{(2x + 9)} + {1}/{2}}\\)", "answer": "4(x + 6)(2x + 9)/3(x + 3)(2x + 17)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{2(x + 6)}/{3(x + 3)}}/{{(2x + 17)}/{2(2x + 9)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({2(x + 6)}/{3(x + 3)} * {2(2x + 9)}/{(2x + 17)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(x + 11)} + {3}/{2}}/{{1}/{(3x + 10)} + 4}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 37)(3x + 10)/2(x + 11)(12x + 41)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(3x + 37)}/{2(x + 11)}}/{{(12x + 41)}/{(3x + 10)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(3x + 37)}/{2(x + 11)} * {(3x + 10)}/{(12x + 41)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{2}/{(4x + 9)} + {1}/{2}}/{{3}/{(2x + 9)} + {1}/{4}}\\)", "answer": "2(4x + 13)(2x + 9)/(4x + 9)(2x + 21)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 13)}/{2(4x + 9)}}/{{(2x + 21)}/{4(2x + 9)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 13)}/{2(4x + 9)} * {4(2x + 9)}/{(2x + 21)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({{3}/{(x + 8)} + 4}/{{1}/{(2x + 1)} + {2}/{3}}\\)", "answer": "3(4x + 35)(2x + 1)/(x + 8)(4x + 5)", "explanation": "Simplify the numerator and denominator\n\\({{(4x + 35)}/{(x + 8)}}/{{(4x + 5)}/{3(2x + 1)}}\\)\nFlip the divisor\n\\({(4x + 35)}/{(x + 8)} * {3(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 5)}\\)\nMultiply the numerators together and the denominators together, then simplify"}
]}